Can animals and people live in Antarctica?
动物和人类能够在南极洲存活吗
Birds, seals, and whales have a shield against cold air and water.
鸟   海豹以及鲸鱼都有自己的庇护所来抵挡寒风和水
Birds have feathers that trap warm air near their bodies for warmth.
鸟的羽毛可以维持自己身体的热量
Seals have fur and a layer of fat that hold in warmth.
海豹的皮毛以及一层脂肪可以让他们保持温暖
Early explorers had a hard time with the harsh setting.
早期的探险家们在严酷的环境下度过了艰难的时光
Lives were lost from lack of food and from being exposed to cold weather.
很多人因为缺乏食物和暴露在寒冷的天气中而丧失生命.
Today people know how to prepare to live there.
如今人们已经懂得如何在那里生活了
Warmer materials have been made for clothing and shelter.
保温材料被用来制作衣服和建造庇护所
But humans still have a difficult time.
但人们的生活依然艰难
Did you know?...
你知道吗
Interesting facts about how animals survive in Antarctica
南极洲的动物们如何生存的趣闻
Animal   Feature
动物    特点
Animal: Penguins
动物    企鹅
Feature: have a thick layer of packed waterproof feathers to keep them warm.
特点   拥有一层厚厚的防水羽毛以保暖
Animal: Insects
动物   昆虫
Feature: have natural antifreeze in their blood to keep them from freezing.
特点   在它们血液中有天然的防冻物质以抵抗寒冷
Animal: Seals
动物   海豹
Feature: are born with white fur to help them blend into the ice and snow.
特点   与生俱来的白色的皮毛能够帮助它们适应冰雪环境
Animal: Polar Bears
动物   北极熊
Feature: have thick claws to help them dig into the ice so they don't slip.
特点   厚厚的爪子能够帮助它们牢牢抓住冰面而不至于滑动